Guide to the School of Hotel Administration Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1949-2008.
Hotel Administration Alumni Affairs and Development Office records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Hotel Administration Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1949-2008.
28-11-4083
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration. Alumni Affairs and Development Office.
3 cubic feet.
Publications, reports.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes reports, meeting minutes, campaign notebooks, press releases, videotapes, DVDs, audiotapes and photographs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes reports, meeting minutes, campaign notebooks, press releases, videotapes, audiotapes and photographs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University -- Alumni and alumnae.; Cornell University -- Students.
Subjects:
Hotel management schools -- New York (State) -- Ithaca
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.; Audiotapes.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Subject Files
  - Press Releases and Public Relations, 1984-1988 (Box 1)
  - Regional Campaign Manual, 1989 (Box 1)
  - HARC Material (Hotel Alumni Regional Campaign), 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - Campaign Status Reports Handbook and Memos, 1980's (Box 1)
  - Regional Campaign Material, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Gala Celebration, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Proposals for Soft Opening and Grand Opening, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Host-A-Donor, 1989 (Box 1)
  - President's Round Table, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Holtzman and Wanderstock Dedications, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Round Table Global Strategies, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Hotel Renovation Kick-Off Material, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Groundbreaking Campaign, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Campaign Kick-Off - Waldorf Astoria, 1985 (Box 1)
  - Recognition Events Committee, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Statler Hotel Grand Opening Letters, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Beech Tree Project, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Binenkorb Dedication, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Donor Recognition, 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - Hotel Plaque Designs, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Public Relations, 1983-1989 (Box 2)
  - School of Hotel Administration Press Releases, 1984-1986 (Box 2)
  - Objectives and Goals, 1980's (Box 2)
  - Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Consultants, 1980's (Box 2)
  - Proposal to the Statler Foundation, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Request for Proposal - Part I, 1986 (Box 2)
  - Campaign Committee Material, 1983-1989 (Box 2)
  - Leadership Campaign Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - Leadership Campaign Subcommittee Minutes, 1985-1988 (Box 2)
  - Campaign Committee Material, 1985-1987 (Box 2)
  - Marketing Meeting Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Case Statement, 1985 (Box 2)
  - Fund Raising Concepts, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Final Campaign Memos and Reports and Sequence of Events, 1985-1990 (Box 2)
- Series II. Tape Recordings and Videocasettes
  - Broten Farewell Party (reel to reel tape), August 1974; tr 10631 (Box 3)
  - Club Wine Tasting - Ballroom (reel to reel tape), May 1977; tr 10632 (Box 3)
  - Unidentified reel to reel tape, no date; tr 10633 (Box 3)
  - 2nd Day (reel to reel tape), October 28, 1978; tr 10634 (Box 3)
  - 3rd Day - Think Forecast (reel to reel tape), October 29, 1978; tr 10635 (Box 3)
  - Henry Fox - Hotel Management Workshop (reel to reel tape), March 1971; tr 10636 (Box 3)
  - James Manning - Economics Lab (reel to reel tape), May 10, 1965; tr 10637 (Box 3)
  - Food Service Industry Workshop (reel to reel tape), 1973; tr 10638 (Box 3)
  - Statler Hall Dedication (reel to reel tape), May 7, 1949; tr 10639 (Box 3)
  - NCR Century Instruction Series - Century Fundamentals - Part 2 Reel B-1, May 1969; tr 10640 (Box 3)
  - NCR Century Instruction Series - Century Fundamentals - Part 2 Reel B-2, May 1969; tr 10641 (Box 3)
  - NCR Century Instruction Series - Century Fundamentals - Part 2 Reel B-3, May 1969; tr 10642 (Box 3)
  - NCR Century Instruction Series - Century Fundamentals - Part 2 Reel B-4, May 1969; tr 10643 (Box 3)
  - NCR Century Instruction Series - Century Fundamentals - Part 2 Reel B-5, May 1969; tr 10644 (Box 3)
  - School of Hotel Administration Groundbreaking - U-matic, October 17, 1986; V 8927 (Box 3)
  - Development Final - U-matic, October 1, 1987; V 8928 (Box 3)
  - Hotel Development - U-matic, 1987; V 8929 (Box 3)
  - Building on a Legacy of Leadership - U-matic, 1987; V 8930 (Box 3)
  - Building on a Legacy of Leadership - Back-up - U-matic, 1987; V 8931 (Box 3)
  - Photos of Hotel Memorabilia that was given away as gifts, no date (Box 3)
  - Videos recorded during a trip by Jon Denison (Associate Dean for External Affairs) to a Summit held in India, 2008; DVD 1859-1874 (Box 3)